[{
    "used": 0,
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is a chocolate dipped Twinkie called?",
    "answer": "Chocodile"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Antananarivo is the capital of what African nation",
    "answer": "Madagascar"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 3,
    "question": "A hutong is a narrow street typically emblematic of what City?",
    "answer": "Beijing"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What element is named for the german word for Gremlin?",
    "answer": "Cobalt"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Who was the first African-American congresswoman?",
    "answer": "Shirley Chisholm"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the mysterious element sought by Joe Chip in a novel by Philip K. Dick, considered one of his most renowned works?",
    "answer": "Ubik"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What form of Japanese theater is derived from the Japanese words for 'talent' or 'skill'?",
    "answer": "Noh"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What geographic feature connects Asia to Africa?",
    "answer": "Isthmus of Suez"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Ginger is an example of what type of horizontally growing underground stem?",
    "answer": "Rhizome"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What car brand translates into 'I roll' in latin",
    "answer": "Volvo"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What collection of poems by Edgar Lee Masters was famous for shedding light on the imperfections of small town USA?",
    "answer": "Spoon River Anthology"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What layer of the atmosphere are we in right now?",
    "answer": "Troposphere"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The divisions between Saturn's rings are named for what astronomer?",
    "answer": "Cassini"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What is the only synthetically created element?",
    "answer": "Technetium"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Created in July 2011, what is the newest country in the world?",
    "answer": "South Sudan"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What would a priest use an aspergil for?",
    "answer": "Sprinkling holy water"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What moody name is the collective term for a group of jellyfish?",
    "answer": "A brood"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What zodiac sign does the opening song to Hair reference?",
    "answer": "Aquarius"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Jules Leotard (for whom the garment is named) was a famous performer of what acrobatic discipline?",
    "answer": "Trapeze"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the only state with a non-rectangular state flag?",
    "answer": "Ohio"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 21,
    "question": "The 1916 Jersey Shore shark attacks served as the inspiration for what novel?",
    "answer": "Jaws"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Walter Gropius was famous for starting what architectural movement?",
    "answer": "Bauhaus"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 23,
    "question": "In baseball, a .200 batting average is the threshold for mediocrity, also called what line?",
    "answer": "Mendoza line"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 24,
    "question": "By what current name do we call the country once known as the Dutch East Indies?",
    "answer": "Indonesia"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What company invented the TV remote?",
    "answer": "Zenith"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What two countries are divided by the 49th parallel",
    "answer": "USA and Canada"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 27,
    "question": "According to the movie Caddyshack, what do you have to do to get in touch with the force in the Universe that makes all things happen?",
    "answer": "Be the ball"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What is the name of the hit 2014 podcast that investigated the curious circumstances behind the death of Hae Min Lee?",
    "answer": "Serial"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Who is the robot who combats the Avengers in their much awaited 2015 sequel?",
    "answer": "Ultron"
}, {
    "used": 0,
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Who has hosted Saturday Night Live the most number of times?",
    "answer": "Alec Baldwin"
}]